[{"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "EIFGJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CFHA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FDCAH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HCJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HIECD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CGF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IAHFJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GHDAI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JCB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to cinema D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IAJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "ACID"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to bank F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FGCD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HCA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GADJB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HFAED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to cinema I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FCH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IHDB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CAG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "G"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GJH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EBDJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "DF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to cinema F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JDI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HJC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "AHG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to cinema G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AIC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "J"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "IA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BHI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EBC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IDA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FGI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DHBF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JADC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JFDG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "ADB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EFBG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EBF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BGJF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "AJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "DF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DFJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to bank G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JFI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EHC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "DAGH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GCJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HJD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CAF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EGC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "DFA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GBDH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to cinema G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JIHFE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "AHJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "AJEI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JAI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to house B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "DF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BEGD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GEDHJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DHE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CFIHGD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JBCE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GFA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HCG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "CJHFGEI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to cinema I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HBACF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "AIG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HBGF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EGC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FGA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BAHGDC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HDB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EHJFC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "HBG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JIDG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HCE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BIH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to house J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FIBE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to cinema G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FAJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BHIF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "EH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "CJBH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "HEGI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JCH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EJB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DAH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GBE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IGJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CFE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to house G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "ADJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "CBH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HEBG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GCJAH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HIB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "CG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "B"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JBC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HCG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to cinema J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "CI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "AHJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DAF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GIFH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "AG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "ECB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AGJF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "ECJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "IEBF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EAD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FIHA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to cinema F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "ABJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IGFA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GDF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "ADI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DHI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EADH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GHJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JAB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "F"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HCEF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HABI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "DA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EAJF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HCI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BHAG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FGD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "DH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "CJFHG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "D"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "AFHBC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BDCJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "ID"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "IJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "BJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JFA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to cinema B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "DI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JDA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DCEFJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CGIJED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "AI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DAC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "AFBJG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FBIHG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CDGBE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JGAH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "AH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "BIGF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GAI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EJB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GIHDBF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JGIH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AIC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "IHB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to cinema I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "ICB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JBADE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "DE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "CE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "AH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CAIJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FBG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JHG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GDC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HFG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BHF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AHI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IDCA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CJGD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GDA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GCA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BGF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to cinema B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GHCIE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "DH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BFDG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GJDB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FHC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to bank F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "DFIHBGC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "DBACGJF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "AIE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BACJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JDC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JGA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HFCJI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IFE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to garden D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CFBH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "AG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GAD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IFG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "EA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HFBED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "ADG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GJD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FBGA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "ADH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IJC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BJHIG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "DF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JBGC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GEIJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "DIFAHGC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to store C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "CJH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FIB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GHI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FDG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "CE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EBAG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HFAJE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "ED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EIG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "CI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JIEG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CAD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JHEI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GCH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HCJBFE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "DI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GEIF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "ABDJI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FJG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HBJD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to house J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FIE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EAJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GCEF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to cinema F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HDGBJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CJED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GBA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BGC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HCDE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "DFC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HFAB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GDBC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "EFB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FEAC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AGIJH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HIG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to cinema F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "ED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IHG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "ED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BJHA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to bank A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "HCDJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FHAG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IFGH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HFI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "CEFH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to cinema B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IHE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to bank F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EDBI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "AEJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "EJD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "CEJG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to cinema I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EHI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BEG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CHIA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FHD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "DAJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HAI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "DE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BJE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to bank C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to cinema D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IAD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "DE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BGHJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HDFB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to garden A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "GCIBD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to cinema D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "EBJIC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GHE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CGFB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to cinema G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EDA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FDC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "AEJCDG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "AJD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to cinema D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BDF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BGA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to house B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FDIB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HFE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AEFBG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to store F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JIC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FED"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EJH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to cinema B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FCDI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JGDA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to school A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "DJGH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "AC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "I"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to house J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IFE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "BHEJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "ID"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BHJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FBCA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to bank E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to school H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to cinema A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "EFA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "EH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "FH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "H"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BACH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CDE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CEI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "BF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to cinema C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "AF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GHDF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "DAFB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store E to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JEG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "GC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to bank I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HBG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store A to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "GEHA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to store E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to house J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IGC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to cinema H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to bank J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to garden H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "CB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to bank B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank B to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "IJAGEF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house A to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "IE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AJGE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "EF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house E to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to school I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "AJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "IGA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank H to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to garden F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CJI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank D to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to garden E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "BA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to house D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "IFCJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to house D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house D to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school J to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "GIB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to store C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school F to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house I to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "JFCD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to bank G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "EDI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house E to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "FIG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden F to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "CI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to store H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "AE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to school G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "JI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to store E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to store I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to school J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to garden H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden H to house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AHFG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema A to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to cinema B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "CAE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to house I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house I to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FHD"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to garden I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden I to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EHIC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to school I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school I to school D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school C to garden F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school C to school B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "JI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to bank B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "GH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to school G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "HIDGC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to bank G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank G to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden B to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "HJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to bank E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank E to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank E to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to bank H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "AE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to house E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "CGA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank I to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "AIH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to garden J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden J to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school I to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank G to house C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "HI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to bank F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank F to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to school B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to school C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to school D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "IF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school E to school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden G to cinema I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to garden B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EDHJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to garden E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden E to bank G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to store C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store C to house I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "JFAE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to garden F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden F to house B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to bank J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank J to garden G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house B to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to store A. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "IC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to store I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store I to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to house F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to store B. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "JAG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to store A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden I to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store A to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "EA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank H to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school G to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to store C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "HA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school F to cinema G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to school E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school E to bank D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank D to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to store A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema G to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to school C. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "FGEDJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to store B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store B to school G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school G to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store H to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to garden D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden D to bank I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to store C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store C to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store F to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "HJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to house B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house B to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank A to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema G to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to bank E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to house F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "ABH"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store E to store B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to bank I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank I to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to bank C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank C to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store B to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "EBJI"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house J to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to store F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house J to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to cinema E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to bank D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "JGBE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to cinema A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to store G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store G to store J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store J to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to house E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema A to store D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store D to school F. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "BADF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store G to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to cinema A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to garden I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to garden H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden H to cinema J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema J to store D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store D to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "GCF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden C to house A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house A to cinema B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema B to cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema B to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest school?", "Answer": "CDIE"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school B to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema D to store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to cinema H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema H to house A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema H to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school B to store I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store I to garden C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden C to school E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "BJHG"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house F to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to house I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house F to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to cinema D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to school E. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema D to cinema J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema J to house H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to bank G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "FC"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is house H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house H to house D. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house D to cinema G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house H to house C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house C to cinema I. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema I to store J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store J to bank A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank A to garden B. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema I to school F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to cinema E. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest store?", "Answer": "HCIJ"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden D to cinema C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to garden B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden B to house J. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema C to garden A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden A to store H. There is a road which is 200 meters long from store H to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to bank F. There is a road which is 200 meters long from bank F to garden G. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "DCAHEF"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school D to cinema E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema E to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to bank J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank J to school F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to store G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema E to school C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school D to house H. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest bank?", "Answer": "DEB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is cinema F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema F to garden A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden A to house C. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house C to bank B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank B to store E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from cinema F to house G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from house G to garden D. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school J to garden I. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest garden?", "Answer": "FA"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is school H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school H to school A. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to cinema B. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to garden E. There is a road which is 200 meters long from garden E to bank C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from bank C to school I. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school H to garden G. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden G to garden J. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest cinema?", "Answer": "HAB"}, {"Story": "There is a set of roads and a set of landmarks. The start point is store F. There is a road which is 100 meters long from store F to house G. There is a road which is 200 meters long from house G to school A. There is a road which is 200 meters long from school A to bank H. There is a road which is 100 meters long from school A to garden J. There is a road which is 100 meters long from garden J to cinema C. There is a road which is 100 meters long from cinema C to store D. ", "Question": "From the start point, how to reach the nearest house?", "Answer": "FG"}]